http://www.delta-therm.com/policies

find your repHomeProductsSnow MeltingRoof De-IcingPipe TracingPermafrost PreventionLoad Switching PanelsFloor WarmingElectric Infrared HeatersSpecs & CADProposal RequestTech SupportAbout UsContactBring us your heat trace challenge and we’ll give you the best solution for your application.Snow Melting • Roof De-Icing • Pipe Tracing • Permafrost Prevention • Floor Warming • Infrared HeatersPrivacy PolicyInformation Collection, Use and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.UpdatesOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (800)526-7887 or here.Request FulfillmentWe ask for information from you on our contact page so that we can respond to your requests for information, meetings, training, consulting or orders. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name, email and business address). This information is used to fulfill your requests. If we have questions regarding your request, we'll use this information to contact you.CookiesWe use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to login a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.SharingWe share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.LinksThis web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information such as name, company and email. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.Need information or the latest catalog? Contact your local rep today.HomeProductsSpecs & CADRequest ProposalTech SupportAbout UsContact UsPoliciesSite MapInstallation GuidesHow-To-VideosEngineering / Design ServicesRequest Information / CatalogOrder Product SamplesCase Studies / White PapersInteractive Full CatalogPre-Install Planning MeetingOn-Site TrainingWiring InspectionService CallProfessional Development Hour (PDH)Admin Login6711 Sands Rd, Suite A • Crystal Lake, IL 60014 • (800) 526-7887 • (847) 526-2407  • Site by BaseZero Studios, LLC.COPYRIGHT © 2000, DELTA-THERM CORPORATION - ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
